cmswatch.com 2019-07-08

# Privacy Policy | Real Story Group

## YOUR PRIVACY IS IMPORTANT TO US

Information gathered by Real Story Group during use of this website may be collected when an individual: 

  * Fills out a form, including but not limited to webinar registration, sample download, newsletter sign up, advisory paper download.
  * Uses any of our decision tools.
  * Purchases certain products or services from us.
  * Contacts us to obtain more information about our products and services.

## WHAT INFORMATION DOES REAL STORY GROUP COLLECT?

  * Personal contact information you may choose to provide while visiting or registering on our site, including events. This information may include your: name, address, company name, job title, telephone number, email address, and the name and email of third parties you may provide to us.
  * Behavioral information about how you use our site and your IP address.

## HOW THIS INFORMTION IS USED?

The Real Story Group facilitates business through communication with clients and other business contacts and uses personal contact information you share with us in the ways noted below. 

**Marketing Purpose:** To send marketing content regarding our services and products which may be of interest and to promote our business and brand. We will only send marketing-related communications if you have consented to receive such communications. You can opt-out of these communications at any time. You can also change your communication preferences. 

**Transactional Communications:** We may send you transactional communications (e.g., service-related announcements, billing-related matters, updates to our Terms of Service or other policies, changes to our services and follow up emails when you register for events or services, etc.). 

**Subscriptions:** To fulfill contractual obligations that may include providing products or services that you or your employer purchased, answer your contract administration related inquiries or communicate with you about your account or transactions with us, and send you information about features on the site, or changes to our policies or events for which you registered. 

**Security:** IP addresses are collected in order to maintain our site security and ensure access to restricted portions of the site is limited to authorized users. 

**Contractual Agreements:** We may also disclose certain data to third party contractors or vendors in connection with their performance of services to us. Contractual agreements between us and such third parties ensure that your information will be kept confidential and secure. 

**Social Media:** If you participate in Real Story Group’s online communities or other shared services, your profile information may be shared with other members to enable collaboration. 

**Event Registration:** When registering for an event you may give consent to receive marketing content post registration, as well as, receive event follow up information. 

**Forward to a Colleague:** You may use the forward-to-colleague functionality on our site or apps to send your colleagues information from Real Story Group or its subsidiaries. In order to fulfil this request, we will ask you for your and your colleagues' names and email addresses. We do not retain this data after the email is sent. Please be aware that your name and e-mail address may be included in the communication sent to your colleague. 

**Customer Support:** We may use your information to manage your account usage. 

## COOKIES

A cookie is a small text file that a website saves on your computer or mobile device when you visit the site. It enables the website to remember your actions and preferences (such as login, language, font size and other display preferences) over a period of time, so you don’t have to keep re-entering them whenever you come back to the site or browse from one page to another. Real Story Group uses the cookies in the ways noted below. 

**Cookies required for access to the site and core functionality. **Cookies do not contain personally identifiable information; however, if you are a registered user, we may store this information with your registration information to enable us to provide a more personalized experience. Use of cookies may also allow Real Story Group to automate your access to password-protected portions of the site, so you don’t have to re-enter your password each time you visit.****

 ** **

**Cookies used to gather behavioral information through the site; **provide customized content and recommendations and analytics. Behavioral information collected by our web analytics vendor Google Analytics is used to analyze data regarding visitor trends and research consumption, so we can plan site enhancements, and measure overall site effectiveness. Aggregated (non-personally identifiable) user behavior collected through cookies may be shared with our other third-party service providers to either analyze or execute marketing programs.****

 ** **

## RETAINING STORED DATA

We generally retain data for as long as you have an account with us, or to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes or enforce our agreements. 

## WHAT YOU CONTROL

  * Change the preferences or settings in your web browser to control cookies or you may choose to control and/or delete all cookies from your hard drive.
  * Unsubscribe from promotional emails you receive at any time by clicking the link at the bottom of the email. You may still receive important service announcements and administrative messages.

## CONTACT US

\ 

Questions, comments and requests regarding this Privacy Policy can be directed to Real Story Group by email: support@realstorygroup.com or by phone in USA & Canada: +1-800-325-6190. Manage your subscription preferences and select or change your contact preferences at any time. 

## LAST UPDATED DEC 11, 2018

We may change and/or update our Privacy Policy. Upon doing so, we will post an updated version on this website. We recommend you regularly review this website to ensure that you are always aware of our information practices and any changes to such. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will go into effect on posting to this page. 

********
